{
    "id": "f2c21a61fa674a5fa1751d84d689cb39",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The poor people ................................... to the will of the tyrant.",
            "description": "Bent is the past tense of bend.",
            "answers": [
                "bent",
                "bended",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d53349e4bbfa486aa6fe4e8552d0913e"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ........................................ him hard until he fell unconscious.",
            "description": "Hit is the past tense of hit. ",
            "answers": [
                "hit",
                "hitted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5271d3c2bd547f1a889bc2afe30e4b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Civil war has .................................... the nation.",
            "description": "Torn is the past participle of tear.",
            "answers": [
                "tore",
                "teared",
                "torn"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75a8cac20b0949039058c2dd1487f100"
        },
        {
            "question": "The puppy ...................................... a hole in the stockings.",
            "description": "Tore is the past tense of tear.",
            "answers": [
                "tore",
                "torn",
                "teared"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f38f8626d2ca4feb88da43552bfeb7a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ........................................ his money in his shoe.",
            "description": "Hid is the past tense of hide.",
            "answers": [
                "hid",
                "hided",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5ab465b23c0446f83f133168522906a"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are searching for ...................................... treasures.",
            "description": "The past participle form of hide is hidden. Here it is used as an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "hid",
                "hided",
                "hidden"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1a84a3e4b2cf44c09b0178e76a18bfbd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly the bomb ....................................",
            "description": "Burst is the past and past participle of burst.",
            "answers": [
                "burst",
                "bursted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6291fc58bdd4b53942dc1d368244c7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................................... my hand while cooking.",
            "description": "Burn can be regular or irregular and the forms burned and burnt are both correct.",
            "answers": [
                "burned",
                "burnt",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e139a0f134dd4dca9dddfa28534a0878"
        },
        {
            "question": "A mosquito just ....................................... me.",
            "description": "Bit is the past tense of bite.",
            "answers": [
                "bite",
                "bited",
                "bit",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ad7e9629e6cc408487f0f8dd422dfcee"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hikers .......................................... their way up the hill.",
            "description": "Wound is the past tense of wind.",
            "answers": [
                "winded",
                "wound",
                "wounded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54b56299b8f245eaa90e20a96d25c7fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ....................................... a diamond necklace to the party.",
            "description": "Wore is the past tense of wear.",
            "answers": [
                "weared",
                "wore",
                "worn"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e1563d968a3415c895b7241d9dccd3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His failure ........................................ his parents.",
            "description": "Upset is the past tense of upset.",
            "answers": [
                "upset",
                "upsetted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b1ea9082493447569d840e3bd53d0188"
        }
    ]
}